adwinks.in 2014-12-19

# Privacy Policy | ibibo Ads

****  
---  
Ibibo Ads (“we” “our” “us") is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users (“user”) and fostering user confidence in the Internet, Internet advertising and direct marketing. We offer a range of Services that allow advertisers and publishers to show online users the most useful and relevant ads online. We continually evaluate innovative ways to protect user privacy while also offering our clients the best solutions regarding their interactions with their customers. 

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide users with clear and complete notice about the user information we may collect in connection with our Services, how we use it and choices we offer.  
  
**1\. Information We Collect Through our Services**  
  
  * **We do not collect Personal Identifiable information:**

We do not collect the online user’s personally identifiable information ("PII") through our Services.  PII generally refers to information such as an individual’s name, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, bank account details, or e-mail address. 

  * **Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected by our Services:**

We may collect non-personally identifiable information ("Non-PII") regarding the user’s behavior and usage patterns on advertisements and sites to improve and customize the type of advertisements user sees on various sites.  Non-PII may include information such as the type of Internet browser used by an online user, the type of computer operating system used, the domain name of the website visited, as well as information related to websites and web pages a user is viewing when an advertisement is shown. 

We collect Non-PII through the use of cookies and pixels.  No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.  A cookie is a file on your browser that uniquely identifies your browser.  A pixel is a line of code which is used by a Web site or third party ad server to track a user’s activity.  The use of a pixel allows us to record that a user has visited a particular webpage along with additional Non-PII that the website publisher or advertiser may choose to include with the pixel. 

  * **Any Information provided by the user :**

Data either entered by you or third party on our clients or a third party’s website  with an intention or interest to avail said services upon agreeing to the privacy policy of that party shall be subject to the privacy policy of such party. We are not liable to you or any third party for any damages that the user or any third party may suffer however arising from your disclosure of Personal Information in any public environment or any third party. You accordingly disclose information in a public environment or to a third party at your own risk. 

We use the information collected from our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve our services, to develop new ones and to protect us and the users. We use this information to improve user experience by presenting customized ads to the user. When showing customized ads we will not associate a cookie or pixels with sensitive categories such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health. 

We require our clients to comply with applicable laws governing online privacy and encourage them to publish privacy policies that tell you about how the information they are gathering is being used. 

**2\. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
We do not collect PII via our Services, and therefore, we do not sell, rent, or share PII collected on our customer’s websites to non-affiliated third parties. 

We may disclose aggregated Non-PII collected through our Services, and information derived from it, to our clients, or persons to process it for us, based on our instruction and in compliance w policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measure.  This Non-PII may be used by our clients to deliver tailored ads to users on participating websites.  This information cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually.  Further, all of our clients have warranted that they shall use any Non-PII they receive in compliance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may disclose a user’s information to third parties when we are obligated to do so by law or government orders to intercept, disclose, monitor, or store any of the Information, in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.   
  
**3\. User Choice**  
We use technology, which includes cookies, in the delivery of our Services.  We believe that the use of these tools enables us and our advertiser clients to provide users with a more meaningful web experience.   
You may at all times adjust your computer’s web browser settings to refuse all cookies, but by doing so you may not be able to use certain features on the websites you visit or take full advantage of all the website offerings and interest based advertising.  You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s "help" file.

You may also simply opt out of receiving interest-based advertising by [**clicking here**](http://ads.ibibo.com/ad/optout.php).   
If you are unable to click on given link please copy & paste **"http://ads.ibibo.com/ad/optout.php"** into your browser. 

If you buy a new computer, upgrade or change Web browsers or delete this "opt-out" cookie, you will need to perform this opt-out process again.  In order for the opt-out to work, your browser must be set to accept 3rd party cookies. Opting out does not necessarily delete or replace all cookies from our domain.   
  
**4\. Data Retention**  
We may maintain Non-PII in an aggregated form for all of our Services for a period longer than five years.   
**5\. Information Security**  
We follow are reasonable steps to protect   to protect against the unauthorized access, use and disclosure of data.  This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic, and management activities required to protect data integrity, access, and use.  Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential information.  However, despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers, no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure.  Therefore, while we strive to protect your data at all times, we cannot guarantee that our systems shall be free from third party interceptions or are incorruptible from viruses and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.   
**6\. Change to this Privacy Policy**  
We may change our privacy policy for the reason but not limited to the changing nature of privacy laws, user needs, and our business, we may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time by providing advance notice on our Web site before implementing such modifications.  Accordingly, since we want to help you clearly understand our Privacy Policy, and any pertinent revisions, we encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to become aware of any changes that may have occurred.  
**7\. Your Use and Correspondence on this Site**  
We use cookies to understand and analyze the usage behavior trends of our users. We do not collect the user’s PII through these cookies, but only non-PII. If you provide us information through our “contact us” link on our corporate website, we will keep a record of the information you provide including your email address and any other personal information you provide solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or to provide you with requested marketing material. This information will never be shared with third parties without your consent .
